Finding Aid for West Side Woman’s Club (Ann Arbor, Mich.) records, 1921-1988
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
West Side Woman’s Club (Ann Arbor, Mich.) records 1921-1988
West Side Woman’s Club (Ann Arbor, Mich.)
1.5 linear feet
85664 Bk 2
Minutes, treasurer's reports, scrapbooks, and other records detailing the activities to this community service organization.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group came from the club (donor no. 2899 )
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
The West Side Woman's Club is an Ann Arbor, Michigan women's service organization. It was formerly called the Third Ward Neighborhood Club.
The records consist of organizational files, including minutes and treasurer's report. There are also scrapbooks detailing club activities.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor (Mich.); Women--Michigan--Ann Arbor--Societies and clubs.; West Side Woman's Club (Ann Arbor, Mich.)
Genre Terms:
Scrapbooks.
- Organizational records
  - Historical Material (Box 1)
  - Administrative Material (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1976-1988 (Box 1)
  - Budgets, 1954-1988 (Box 1)
  - Community Achievement Contest, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 1)
  - Directories, 1947, 1966-1988 (Box 1)
  - Minute books
    - 1921-1923 (Box 1)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 1)
    - 1926-1932 (Box 1)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 1)
    - 1937-1943 (Box 1)
    - 1943-1947 (Box 1)
  - Minutes
    - 1976-1983 (Box 1)
    - 1983-1988 (Box 1)
  - Treasurer's Reports
    - 1970-1979 (Box 1)
    - 1979-1988 (Box 1)
- Scrapbooks
  - 1949-1958 (Box 2)
  - 1958-1960 (Box 2)
  - 1961-1965 (Box 2)
  - 1924-1956 (Box 2)